<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SUBOFICIAL</string>
    <string name="proyecto">Project</string>
    <string name="titulo">"DEVELOPMENT OF A BASIC SYSTEM OF INFOCOMMUNICATION AND DISPLAY OF DATA THROUGH MOBILE DEVICES WITH ANDROID TECHNOLOGY "</string>
    <string name="escuela">"NAVAL SCHOOL OF SUBOFICIAL ARC BARRANQUILLA "</string>
    <string name="tecnologiaelectronica">"ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGY "</string>
    <string name="ciudadfecha">"BARRANQUILLA, APRIL 2018 "</string>
    <string name="contenido">Content</string>
    <string name="guardar">Save</string>
    <string name="variable3">Variable 3rd</string>
    <string name="variable2">Variable 2nd</string>
    <string name="variableuno">Variable 1st</string>
    <string name="refrescar">Refresh</string>
    <string name="titulovariables">REAL-TIME CONNECTION VIA WEB-XBEE</string>
    <string name="justificacionfull">"It is intended to develop a data transfer system, which remotely transmits from the device, to an android platform mobile application, all the information collected, using an Xbee Pro 900Hp SB3 module, which takes advantage of the DigiMesh network protocol ®, which offers dense network operation and support for sleeper routers, which is also available in a patented point-to-multipoint configuration. It consists of a power of 250 mW, a band of 902 MHz to 928 MHz, so it can reach up to 14.4Km (with 2.1dB dipole antenna), channel mask selectable for software immunity and in addition to its industrial temperature rating ( -40ºC to 85ºC). It is intended to communicate through an arduino and a main receiver that will load the data collected in the cloud. At the same time, the phone containing the application will be able to access the registered data in real time, only with an internet connection, from any point of geographical location. All this for research, information and prevention of catastrophic events. "</string>
    <string name="variables">Variables</string>
    <string name="justificacion">Justification</string>
    <string name="planteamiento">Approach</string>
    <string name="introduccion">"Introduction "</string>
    <string name="agradecimientos">Thankss</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_inicio">Start</string>
    <string name="title_activity_objetivos">Objectives</string>
    <string name="title_activity_justificacion">Justification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_planteamiento_problema">"Approach Problem "</string>
    <string name="title_activity_introduccion">Introduction</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_agradecimientos">Thanks</string>
    <string name="inicio">Start</string>
    <string name="ciudadfecha2">BARRANQUILLA, MAY 2018</string>
    <string name="bibliografia">Bibliography</string>
    <string name="objetivos">Objetives</string>
    <string name="introduccionfull">"Communication methods such as cell phones, radio and the Internet use advanced technology in wireless data transmission systems, which carry invisible electromagnetic waves to transmit data from great distances in a short time. There are several wireless data transmission systems that allow data signals to be sent and received by other units quickly. Currently we handle many kinds of data and information, in any of the areas that we can think of, be they daily or unusual. For example, things as common as are the state of the weather, weather, economic statistics, the values ​​of some objects or food, or rather information about what is happening around the world and so on. Generalizing all the types of data and information that we receive daily, it is very important to bear in mind that we must have an adequate management of all this. All means must be used to take full advantage of the information, regardless of where it comes from. We can count on the transfer of information through many channels, television, radio, internet and among others. Also taking into account that not all information is of the same type, therefore each must have a specific management, that is, I can not give the same handling to public information as to private information, since this may contain data, confidential, personal or things like that. It is important to have security systems that guarantee that my information will be transmitted in a secure manner, from the sender to the receiver, regardless of the medium or the interferences that are encountered during the tour, therefore the importance of developing methods in which we can transmit or share information from one point to another taking into account factors such as means, speed and security. Xbee data transfer modules via RF, were selected to perform our project, due to its accessibility, capacity, resistance, range, portability and low power consumption, since it allows us to have a long-range, additional coverage of a good data transfer speed handling connections of up to 250Kbps at distances of around 28 miles with high gain antennas. Also taking into account that they can be used in point-to-point and point-to-multipoint connection forming a mesh connection that also allows us a better coverage. "</string>
    <string name="objetivosfull">"GENERAL OBJECTIVE • Design and build a system of infocommunication, acquisition and monitoring of data, from a remote device to a mobile application. 3.2 SPECIFIC OBJECTIVES • Consult background or relevant information for the design and implementation of a mobile application. • Design a mobile application for the transmission of data between a device and the client. • Implement a mobile application for the transmission of data between a device and the client. "</string>
    <string name="bibliografiafull">•\tOjeda, L. (2009). MÓDULOS DE TRANSMISIÓN INALÁMBRICA. Recuperado de http://www.xbee.cl  •\tTECHNOHALL. (2012). REDES INALÁMBRICAS. Recuperado de http://technohall.com/2012/05/tips-para-implementar-redes-inalambricas-de-sensores-con-xbee/   •\tZIGBEE. (2012) TECNOLOGÍA ZIGBEE. Recuperado de http://dspace.epn.edu.ec/bitstream/15000/8637/2/T10110CAP2.pdf  •\tDIGI. (2012). MANUAL BÁSICO DE USO DEL SOFTWARE X-CTU. Recuperado de http://www.digi.com/support/productdetail?pid=3352.  •\tARDUINO (2012). ARDUINO UNO R3. Recuperado de http://arduino.cc/en/Main/ArduinoBoardUno  •\tARDUINO (2012). MANUAL BÁSICO DE PROGRAMACIÓN ARDUINO. Recuperado de http://code.google.com/p/arduino/wiki/BuildingArduino</string>
    <string name="integrantes">Members</string>
    <string name="agradecimientosfull">We will always remember, the day we entered this Institution of Higher Academic - Military Education with High Quality Accreditation, which forged us as Marines of Honor and Discipline. In this project we want to thank first of all our heavenly father GOD for the wisdom and understanding for the pro activity of each activity since the beginning of our military career. That led to an excellent result, our parents for their unconditional support, so it was a voice of encouragement that motivation motivated to complete this achievement. I show my most sincere thanks to my specialty tutors, to our professional advisors who guided us and promoted their advanced knowledge, being an essential key piece for each stage of learning the development of work. To my colleagues, who through time we were strengthening a friendship and creating a family, to share experiences, joys, frustrations, cries, sadness, fights, celebrations and multiple factors that helped that today we are as a family. I know that these words are not enough to express my gratitude, but I hope that with them, they give to understand my feelings of appreciation and affection to all of them.</string>
    <string name="planteamientodelproblema">"Unlike the SCADAT data acquisition systems in which the user interacts with the information provided, an infocommunication system informs and communicates through any ICT technology, to know about environmental conditions, for example, what it supplies us with a system for measuring conditions related to the environment. The appropriate visualization of this information allows us, in a military environment, to know different parameters or conditions related to the military future; allowing decisions to be made not only according to the circumstances related to them; but those related to defense and security, allowing to perform tasks of monitoring, monitoring, monitoring and control, for preventive purposes or for investigative purposes. We find that there are not many remote, easily acquired means to obtain this data, because the technology of the current equipment is very expensive or is not available to everyone. "</string>
    <string name="datostiemporeal">Real-time data</string>
</resources>